KATHLEEN MONTESANO

WEB DEVELOPER

INFO

PHONE

484-505-6968

EMAIL

kathleen.m.montesano@gmail.com

LINKS

GitHub

Website

LinkedIn

SKILLS

HTML5 & CSS3

JavaScript

jQuery

Node

LANGUAGES

Spanish - Conversational

PROFILE

Frontend Developer who brings experience working with HTML, CSS, Javascript, jQuery, and Node. Graduate of the Full Stack Penn LPS Coding Bootcamp. Brings experience obtained through working in Nonprofit and Education to constantly learn and improve upon existing processes. Passionate about programming, I also bring strong communication skills and creativity into my work. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

EDUCATION

Penn LPS Coding Bootcamp

Philadelphia

Jan 2019 - Jul 2019

Evergreen State College, Bachelor of Arts

Olympia,

2005 - 2009

WA

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Program Coordinator, Achieve Now

Philadelphia

Nov 2015 - May 2018

- Training and overseeing volunteers and employees
- Tracking data clearly and efficiently
- Acting as a liaison between Achieve Now and various school partners

Teacher/Coordinator, English Academy Sep 2012 - Aug 2014

Quetzaltenango, Guatemala

- Communicating with prospective and current parents in Spanish
- Developing and executing interactive curriculum

English Teacher, E Bo Young Talking Club

Aug 2010 - Aug 2011

Mokpo, South Korea

- Creating and executing exams
- Keeping students engaged and motivated